

# **PROFILE**

Hello Everyone! I welcome you all in my official resume paper. To introduce myself, recently I have been studying Bachelor of Information Technology at Phoenix College of Management. I have two year of working experiences as a **Data Analyst** and **Data Manager** at one of the reputed E-commerce Website namely **Online Saathi**. In the field of IT, I have good skills and knowledge of following programs.

# **CONTACT**

#### PHONE:

+977 9816246451

#### WEBSITE:

kshitijbishokarma.com.np

#### **EMAIL:**

kshitizbabik.37@gmail.com

## **HOBBIES**

Programming Photography Designing Reading Novel

# KSHITIJ BISHOKARMA

# Student

Bachelor of Information Technology Phoenix College of Management Kathmandu, Nepal (Lincoln University Affiliates)

## **EDUCATION**

# **Mount Everest School**

2010 - 2017

I have completed my secondary level of education from my own birth place namely Chandrapur-3, Rautahat with GPA 3.55(A)

## **Liverpool Int'l College**

2017 - 2019

I have completed my 10+2 level of education choosing major subject 'Biology' from Science faculty in Kathmandu with GPA 2.97(B+).

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Softech Solution [File Manager]

2019

I have worked around 6 months here and my main job is to handle all the data and file and place it in the systematic order.

## Online Saathi [Data Analyst]

2020 - 2021

I have to analyze all the website data with comparison to other e- commerce websites. I have to guide other team member in price fixing in new entry product. Even I have to looked after EMI form and find better process for settlement.

# Seshra Innovation [Website Design]

2021 - Present

I have done internship for around 6 months in Graphics and Website Design and make myself able to design basic designs.

## **SKILLS**

